Contact

lenhenke@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lenhenke (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing BLS ACLS

Len Henke

Nurse Manager Emergency Department

Asheville, North Carolina Area

Summary

Experienced Emergency Department Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Education, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Emergency Medicine, and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional with a Master's Degree focused in Nursing from Tennessee State University.

Experience

Mission Health

4 years 4 months

Nursing Manager March 2020 - Present (4 months)

Administrative House Supervisor March 2019 - March 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Emergency Room Nurse March 2016 - March 2019 (3 years 1 month)

Randstad USA Travel RN September 2015 - March 2016 (7 months)

Travel RN in the Emergency Department

Duke Lifepoint-Harris Regional Hospital Director of Emergency Services January 2015 - October 2015 (10 months) Sylva, NC

Tennessee Board of Regents
Adjunct Faculity
May 2012 - March 2015 (2 years 11 months)
Nashville,TN

Taught Advanced Assessment to 2nd year graduate FNP students

Metro General Hospital 5 years 10 months

Assistant Director of Nursing October 2013 - January 2015 (1 year 4 months) Nashville, TN

Emergency Department RN April 2009 - October 2013 (4 years 7 months) Charge Nurse, ER

Vanderbilt University Medical Center
Emergency Department and Trauma/Critical Care RN
August 2007 - October 2008 (1 year 3 months)
Level I ER and Level I Trauma ICU RN

Johnson City Medical Center Staff RN Emergency Room August 2004 - August 2007 (3 years 1 month) Johnson City, Tennessee

Level I ER RN

Education

Tennessee State University

Master's Degree, Nursing · (2010 - 2012)

East Tennessee State University

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2004 - 2006)

Southwestern Community College
Associate's Degree, Practical Nursing, Vocational Nursing and Nursing
Assistants · (2003 - 2004)